[{"answer": "Hey, you are the couch tonight, young lady. You were all over my side", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "C'mon, I was sleeping with one cheek off the bed", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "By the way, you're falling way behind on the 'I love you's.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No, it's 1", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I don't know that!  my friend's my friend is a dog", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'll get the short stack", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yeah. I mean, his upper lip landed flush on my upper lip. But his lower lip landed well below my rim", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yeah. Definite moisture", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I respect that.  Mmm, what happened", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yeah? What was it", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Uncle my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Hello", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What are you talking about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You got married? I wasn't invited? Nobody sends me an invitation", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "No, no, it was a small ceremony", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yes, yes, you have", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "\", \"dependency_gramma", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "It was nothing, forget it.", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "C'mon, I'm sitting!", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I didn't do anything with it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, it's not here, it was here yesterday", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I'm looking in the first drawer. It's not here", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I told her you'd get married. She thought you'd never do it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I'm not talking loud", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, whoopie whoop.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yeah.  I'll get it, I'll get it! Take it easy, why are you so tired", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Hey, I'm sorry about all that can opener stuff", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Love you", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Aha. Aha. Could it be because you don't want him to know that you have a friend who pees in the shower, is that it?", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Why couldn't you just wait", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Since when is a drain a toilet?", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Alright", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Alright, I'll pick it up, but it's the last time I'm doin' it", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Oh, about thirteen dollars", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Wife.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Well, I'm sorry.  my friend and my friend at the health club. A sweaty my friend is exercising on a leg machine", "qsentId": 36}]